{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Permeability is the inverse equivalent of which electrical term?", "opta": "Voltage", "optb": "Current", "optc": "Resistance", "optd": "Conductance", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which electromagnetic device uses brushes and a commutator?", "opta": "A speaker", "optb": "A dc generator", "optc": "A relay", "optd": "A solenoid", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the flux density of a magnetic field whose flux is 3000 \u00b5Wb and cross-sectional area is 0.25 m2?", "opta": "12,000 T", "optb": "83,330 T", "optc": "0 T", "optd": "More information is needed in order to find flux density.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How much flux is there in a magnetic field when its flux density is 5000 T and its cross-sectional area is 300 mm2?", "opta": "16.67 mWb", "optb": "5.0 Wb", "optc": "3.0 mWb", "optd": "1.5 Wb", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What are the effects of moving a closed wire loop through a magnetic field?", "opta": "A voltage is induced in the wire.", "optb": "A current is induced in the wire.", "optc": "The polarity across the wire depends on the direction of motion.", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Hall effect", "opta": "is a phenomenon with no practical applications", "optb": "is used in various sensor applications", "optc": "can develop potentials of thousands of volts", "optd": "is the basis for solar cell operation", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "\"Series\" and \"parallel\" as applied to dc motors refer to", "opta": "the connection of the motor and controller", "optb": "the connection of the field coil and armature windings", "optc": "the connection of the brush and commutator", "optd": "the connection of the motor batteries", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The component that produces power in an electromagnetic generator is called the", "opta": "armature", "optb": "field winding", "optc": "commutator", "optd": "brush", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the magnetomotive force in a 150-turn coil of wire with 2 A flowing through it?", "opta": "13.33 mAt", "optb": "300 At", "optc": "75 At", "optd": "152 At", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A Hall effect sensor", "opta": "exists only in theory", "optb": "is a noncontacting magnetic sensor", "optc": "can operate only a few times before failure", "optd": "produces very large voltages", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which two values are plotted on a B-H curve graph?", "opta": "Reluctance and flux density", "optb": "Permeability and reluctance", "optc": "Magnetizing force and permeability", "optd": "Flux density and magnetizing force", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which electromagnetic device has a flexible cone?", "opta": "A speaker", "optb": "A dc generator", "optc": "A relay", "optd": "A solenoid", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the reluctance of a material that has a length of 0.045 m, a cross-sectional area of 0.015 m2, and a permeability of 2500 \u00b5Wb/At\u00b7m?", "opta": "833.33 \u00b5At/Wb", "optb": "0.27 At/Wb", "optc": "1200 At/Wb", "optd": "More information is needed in order to find the reluctance.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The unit of flux density is known as", "opta": "magnetomotive force", "optb": "a weber", "optc": "a maxwell", "optd": "a tesla", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What do you call the characteristic of a magnetic material whereby a change in magnetization lags the application of a magnetizing force?", "opta": "Hysteresis", "optb": "Induction", "optc": "Retentivity", "optd": "Reluctance", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which electromagnetic device has a movable iron core called a plunger?", "opta": "A speaker", "optb": "A dc generator", "optc": "A relay", "optd": "A solenoid", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which electromagnetic device contains an armature?", "opta": "A speaker", "optb": "A dc generator", "optc": "A relay", "optd": "A solenoid", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The polarity of induced voltage while a field is collapsing is", "opta": "independent of the force creating the field", "optb": "opposite to the force creating the field", "optc": "identical to the force creating the field", "optd": "present only if the force is stationary", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}